A Guide to the Rockefeller Archive Center records, Topical Surveys FA1499
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Archive Center records, Topical Surveys
1981-1995
Rockefeller Archive Center
FA1499
0.44 Cubic Feet 1 document box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
Arrangement
Chronological.
Scope and Contents
Consists of published surveys of manuscript sources at the Rockefeller Archive Center on a number of topics. Surveys were prepared by Archive Center staff, or by individual scholars (when noted). Some of these surveys were prepared in conjunction with conferences held at or sponsored by the RAC.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 792.
- A Survey of Manuscript Sources for the History of Nursing and Nursing Education at the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1981 May (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Selected Bibliography on the Rockefeller Family and their Organizations, 1894-1980, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A Survey of Manuscript Sources for the History of Nursing and Nursing Education at the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1984 August (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A Survey of Manuscript Sources for the History of Psychiatry and Related Areas in the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1985 June (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A Survey of Sources for the History of Labor and Industrial Relations at the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1985 August (Box 1, Folder 5)
- A Survey of Manuscript Sources for the History of Nursing at the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1985 September (Box 1, Folder 6)
- A Survey of Sources for the History of Labor and Industrial Relations in the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1986 December (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Chinese Science: Using the Rockefeller Archives for Research on Modern Chinese Natural Science, by. Laurence A. Schneider, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- A Survey of Sources for the History of Child Studies at the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Archives of the China Medical Board and the Peking Union Medical College at the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- A Survey of Sources for the History of Nursing at the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1989 April (Box 1, Folder 11)
- A Survey of Sources for the History of Labor and Industrial Relations at the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1989 December (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Forty-Seven Rockefeller Philanthropies (Box 1, Folder 13)
- A Survey of Manuscript Sources for the History of Psychiatry and Related Areas in the Rockefeller Archive Center - master (Box 1, Folder 14)
- A Survey of Sources at the Rockefeller Archive Center for the Study of African-American History and Race Relations, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Sources at the Rockefeller Archive Center on the Transfer and Diffusion of Agricultural Technology by the General Education Board and the International Education Board, 1902-1960, 1989 January, Revised 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)